Guide to the Roy Eaton papers, 1860-2016 and undated. RL.11520
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1955-2014 and undated; 7
  - Audio Tape Reels, 1955-1991 and undated; 4
    - Benton & Bowles--Pampers, Crest, Pepto-Bismol, 1963-1969 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-013)
    - Benton & Bowles--Post (General Foods), 1961-1964 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-014)
      Crispy Critters; Post Toasties; Sugar Crisp; Grape Nuts; Alpha-Bits; Post Oat Flakes; Post Top Three
    - Benton & Bowles--Post (General Foods), 1965-1967 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-015)
      Alpha-Bits; Raisin Bran; Honeycomb
    - Benton & Bowles--Post (General Foods), 1967-1968 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-016)
      Alpha-Bits; Sugar Crisp; New products; Mr. Muscle; Oat Flakes; Peanut Puffs; Post Tens; Corn Crackos; Honeycomb; Fortified Oat Flakes
    - Benton & Bowles--Post (General Foods), 1968-1969 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-017)
      Alpha Bits; Grape Nuts; Honeycomb; Sugar Crisp
    - Benton & Bowles--Prell, 1962-1969 (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-018)
    - Compilation--Musical Commercials (77 tracks), 1955-1959 (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-019)
    - Compilation--Reel 2: Benton & Bowles good takes, 1960 (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-020)
      Columbia Records; Yuban; Post; Zest; IMH
    - Compilation--Reel 3: Benton & Bowles good takes, 1960-1961 (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-021)
      IMH; Yuban; AMEX; Gaines Gravy Train; Zest
    - Compilation--Reel 4: Benton & Bowles good takes, 1962 (Box AV4, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-022)
      IMH; Yuban; Harvey's Bristol Cream; Prell
    - Compilation--Reel 5: Benton & Bowles good takes, 1962 (Box AV5, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-023)
      Texaco; IMH; Harvey's Bristol Cream; Zest; Benson & Hedges; Yuban
    - Compilation--Reel 10: Benton & Bowles good takes, 1962-1963 (Box AV5, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-024)
      Texaco; Parliament; Yuban; Zest; Prell
    - Compilation--Reel 12: Benton & Bowles good takes, 1963 (Box AV5, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-025)
      Beech-Nut
    - Compilation--Reel 13: Benton & Bowles good takes, 1964 (Box AV5, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-026)
      Prell; Paxton; Yuban; Texaco; Chiffon; Sweeta; Sodaburst; Pledge
    - Compilation--Reel 14: Benton & Bowles good takes, 1964 (Box AV5, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-027)
      Prell; Post Toasties; Linus the Lionhearted
    - Compilation--Reel 16: Benton & Bowles good takes, 1964 (Box AV6, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-028)
      Linus the Lionhearted master
    - Compilation--Reel 20: Benton & Bowles good takes, 1966 (Box AV6, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-029)
      Texaco, Zest; Chiffon music
    - Compilation reel, 1973 (Box AV6, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-030)
      Texaco; Zest; Woodrich; Unicom; UNICEF; Unguentine
    - Compilation reel, 1982 (Box AV6, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-031)
      Texaco spots
    - Chrysler, 1988 (Box AV6, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-032)
    - Chrysler "Killer Joe", 1989 (Box AV7, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-033)
    - Crest; Pampers; Pepto Bismol, 1963-1969 (Box AV7, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-034)
    - Compilation G-P, 1971 (Box AV7, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-035)
      Orange Plus; Peter Paul; Pepto Bismol; Lemon Pledge; Post Grape Nuts; Super Sugar Crisp; GCMI Radio; Gillette; Glade; Hasbro; Kentite
    - Compilation--Commercials A-G, 1974 (Box AV7, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-036)
      Brim; Champion; Charmin; Continental Airlines; Cool Whip; Gentle Bay; Gillette; Pledge; Grape Nuts
    - Compilation--Commercials U-Z, 1971 (Box AV7, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-037)
      Unguentine; Unsell War; Yardley; Zest
    - Compilation, 1975 (Box AV7, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-038)
      Pampers; Charmin; E.F. Hutton; Rely; Texaco; Unguentine
    - Crest, 1968 (Box AV8, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-039)
    - Compilation--Benton & Bowles reel 5, 1981-1982 (Box AV8, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-040)
      Schlitz Malt Liquor; Texaco; Texas Commerce Bank; Top Choice; Topex; Wondra; Yuban; Zest
    - Compiled master 2 (14 spots), 1975 (Box AV8, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-041)
    - Compiled master 1, 1975 (Box AV8, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-042)
      Continental; Texaco; Charmin; Hasbro; Ocusol
    - Compiled master (15 spots), 1974 (Box AV8, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-043)
    - Compiled master (14 spots), 1969-1971 (Box AV8, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-044)
    - Compilation, 1974-1979 (Box AV9, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-045)
      Hasbro; Post Sugar Crisp; Kleen & Shine; Horizon; Continental
    - Compilation: Johnson Wax; Parliament, 1958-1959 (Box AV9, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-046)
    - Compilation--Benton & Bowles, 1973 (Box AV9, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-047)
      Robert Hall; Prell; Post Sugar Crisp; Nyquil; Pampers; Peter Paul; Post cereals
    - Compilation--"Reel 1", 1974-1986 (Box AV9, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-048)
      Air Force; Alex; Apollo; AT&T; Beechnut baby food; Beefaroni; Black & Decker; Burger Chef; Cella Wine; Chrysler; Classic Beer; Coffeemate; Crest; Daisy; Data General; Dodge; Drunk Driving; Eckrich cheese; Fairbrooke; First Fidelity
    - Compilation--"Reel 2", 1977-1987 (Box AV9, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-049)
      Hasbro; Jackson Tea; Kodak; Kentucky Fried Chicken; Marine Midland; Moondreamers; Newsweek; Oil of Olay
    - Compilation--"Reel 3", 1979-1986 (Box AV10, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-050)
      Pantene; Pepto Bismol; Post Honeycomb; Planters; Ringling Brothers; Runner Up; Schmidt's; Spectra Vision; Sports Channel
    - Compilation--"Reel 4", 1982-1988 (Box AV10, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-051)
      Texas Commerce Bank; Texaco; United Way; USPS; Vidal Sassoon; Wendy's; Wisk; Diners Club; Centers for Disease Control; Big Brothers and Big Sisters; Chrysler; Pepsi; Pantene
    - Compilation--"Reel 5", 1982-1985 (Box AV10, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-052)
      AT&T; Burger King; Diet Sun; Eckrich; Fairbrooke Coats; Golden Books; Hardee's
    - Compilation--"Reel 6", 1978-1983 (Box AV10, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-053)
      Hardee's; Ringling Bros.; Spectra Video; Newsweek; Burger King; Woman's Day; New Moondreamers; Romper Room
    - Concert--Klavierabend: Roy Eaton The Meditative Chopin reel 1, 1985 (Box AV10, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-054)
    - Concert--Klavierabend: Roy Eaton The Meditative Chopin reel 2, 1985 (Box AV10, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-055)
    - Concert--The Meditative Chopin, 1985 (Box AV11, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-056)
    - Concert--The Meditative Chopin reel 1 spliced master, 1986 (Box AV11, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-057)
    - Concert--The Meditative Chopin reel 2 spliced master, 1986 (Box AV11, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-058)
    - Concert--Roy Eaton piano, Meditative Chopin, 1985 (Box AV11, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-059)
    - Concert--Roy Eaton piano, Meditative Chopin, 1985 (Box AV11, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-060)
    - Concert--Roy Eaton Suhr concert: Bach, Mozart; Chopin, 1986 (Box AV11, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-061)
    - Former Clients, 1962-1963 (Box AV12, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-062)
      Beechnut; Caprolan; IMH; Yuban; Benson & Hedges; Harvey's Bristol Cream
    - Fred Shannon (Shannon Two Feathers) master, 1971 (Box AV12, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-063)
    - Jingle reel, 1986 (Box AV12, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-064)
    - Jingles only, 1988 (Box AV12, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-065)
      Newsweek; Air Force; Moon Dreamers; Kentucky Fried Chicken; AIDS; Big Brothers; Honeycomb; Hardee's; Beefaroni; Lite Brite; Burger King
    - Next Stop 28, undated (Box AV12, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-066)
    - Roy Eaton, undated (Box AV12, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-067)
    - Roy Eaton--Kentucky Fried Chicken (11 spots), 1987 (Box AV13, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-068)
    - Roy Eaton--Pepsi, 1988 (Box AV13, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-069)
    - Roy Eaton--Right Tools Right Hands, undated (Box AV13, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-070)
    - Roy Eaton reel 1, 1978 (Box AV13, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-071)
    - Roy Eaton--Right Tools Right Hands (1" audiotape) (Box AV13, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-072)
    - Roy Eaton reel 2, 1978 (Box AV14, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-073)
    - Roy Eaton reel 3, 1978 (Box AV14, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-074)
    - Roy Eaton reel 4, 1978 (Box AV14, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-075)
    - Roy Eaton classical piano reel 1, 1981 (Box AV14, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-076)
    - Roy Eaton classical piano reel 2, 1981 (Box AV14, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-077)
    - Roy Eaton classical piano 1 of 3 (1/2" audiotape), 1981 (Box AV14, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-078)
    - Roy Eaton classical piano 2 of 3 (1/2" audiotape), 1981 (Box AV15, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-079)
    - Roy Eaton classical piano 3 of 3 (1/2" audiotape), 1981 (Box AV15, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-080)
    - Roy Eaton classical piano Dolby master, 1981 (Box AV15, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-081)
    - Roy Eaton piano, undated (Box AV15, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-082)
    - Roy Eaton scoring reel, 1989 (Box AV15, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-083)
    - Roy Eaton solo piano reel 1 (1/2" audiotape), 1978 (Box AV16, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-084)
    - Roy Eaton solo piano reel 2 (1/2" audiotape), 1978 (Box AV16, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-085)
    - Roy Eaton solo piano reel 3 (1/2" audiotape), 1978 (Box AV16, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-086)
    - Roy Eaton solo piano reel 4 (1/2" audiotape), 1978 (Box AV16, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-087)
    - Roy Eaton solo piano outtakes (1/2" audiotape), 1978 (Box AV17, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-088)
    - Roy Eaton solo piano outtakes and edited parts (1/2" audiotape), 1978 (Box AV17, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-089)
    - South Africa, 1985 (Box AV17, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-090)
      Zulu traditional; Sotho; Religious choral; Zulu Umbaqanca; Umbaqanca pop; Umbaqanca jazz
    - Sports Channel 6 spots, 1984 (Box AV17, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-091)
    - Sports Channel 8 spots, 1984 (Box AV17, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-092)
    - TNT Sunday Nitro, 1990 (Box AV18, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-093)
    - United Way spots, 1986 (Box AV18, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-094)
    - Up the Avenue, 1960 (Box AV18, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-095)
    - Vidal Sassoon, 1985 (Box AV18, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-096)
    - Vidal Sassoon, 1985 (Box AV18, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-097)
    - Virgin, undated (Box AV18, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-098)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Dodge, Crisco (2" master tape), 1988 (Box AV19, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-099)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Chrysler 1 of 2 (2" master tape), 1989 (Box AV19, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-100)
    - AIDS PSA, undated (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-101)
    - Arlene Gold: I Cannot Be Your Friend, undated (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-102)
    - Benton & Bowles--Linus the Lionhearted, 1964 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-103)
    - Benton & Bowles--Linus the Lionhearted print takes, 1964 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-104)
    - Benton & Bowles--Jean Nate, 1979 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-105)
    - Benton & Bowles--Mohawk, 1972 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-106)
    - Benton & Bowles--Texaco "Nice Guys" demo, 1976 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-107)
    - Benton & Bowles--Texaco auditions, 1977 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-108)
    - Bill Hunter tape, undated (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-109)
    - Bitter Sweet--Leslie Shuman, 1979 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-110)
    - Dark and Lovely, undated (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-111)
    - Disco Freak second remix, 1979 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-112)
    - Disco Freak remix 1, 1979 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-113)
    - Fred Shannon (Shannon Two Feathers) compilation, undated (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-114)
      Yellow Hand; White Man; Wounded Knee; Willow Coats; Color Me
    - Gwen Conley--Disco Freak; Love Will Come Again, 1979 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-115)
    - Gwen Conley--Disco Freak; Love Will Come Again, 1979 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-116)
    - Infinity Factory--Bonus auditions, 1977 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-117)
    - Infinity Factory--Compilation 9 tracks, 1977 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-118)
    - Infinity Factory--Compilation 11 tracks, 1977 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-119)
    - Infinity Factory--Compilation 7 tracks, 1977 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-120)
    - Infinity Factory--Reel 1 (11 tracks), 1977 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-121)
    - Infinity Factory--reel 2 (13 tracks), 1977 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-122)
    - Jacques Roc--Ladder of Love; Love Will Come Again, 1979 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-123)
    - Jacques Roc--Master tape, undated (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-124)
    - Jacques Roc--Now Is the Time for Love, 1979 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-125)
    - Jacques Roc--Sunset, 1980 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-126)
    - Let Love In, undated (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-127)
    - Love is God, undated (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-128)
    - Life Is a Game of Pool (Neil Shepherd), 1979 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-129)
    - Newsweek demo 11 tracks, 1985 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-130)
    - Roy Eaton demo (Bill Soden), 1979 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-131)
      Bow Down Before the Sun; Me 'n You; You Touch the World Today (disco); Autumn Day (disco)
    - Roy Eaton--Brighter Day, undated (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-132)
    - Roy Eaton--Like I Love You, undated (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-133)
    - Roy Eaton Music--A Soldier's Lament, 1968 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-134)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Battle Ball, 1989 (Box AV20, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-135)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Battle Ball, 1989 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-136)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Battle Ball remix, 1989 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-137)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Chase Manhattan, 1990 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-138)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Chrysler: Jeep; Dodge Stealth, 1990 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-139)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Hasbro Lite Brite, 1988 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-140)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Just for Men radio, 1989 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-141)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Ore Ida :15, 1991 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-142)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Scoring reel and jingle reel, 1987 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-143)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Scoring reel, undated (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-144)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Special project music for Murray Bruce film, undated (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-145)
    - Roy Eaton Music--Willie Strickland demo 12 tracks, undated (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-146)
    - Roy Eaton performance--1920s, undated (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-147)
    - Roy Eaton performance--1920s, undated (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-148)
    - Roy Eaton performance--A Mighty Fortress (with Cincinnati Choir), 1966 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-149)
    - Roy Eaton performance--A Soldier's Lament, 1968 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-150)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Bach Toccata and Fugue in D Minor, undated (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-151)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Believe, 1968 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-152)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Compilation, 1979 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-153)
      Nocturne in C# minor; Mazurka in F# minor; Mazurka in Bb minor; Scherzo in Bb minor
    - Roy Eaton performance--Compilation, 1979 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-154)
      Nocturne in Bb minor; Ballade in G minor; Liszt in En Reve
    - Roy Eaton performance--Compilation (Fred), undated (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-155)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Concert at Hollis Church, 1974 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-156)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Extended recording instrumental, undated (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-157)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Fort Dix Recital Hall, 1955 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-158)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Fort Dix Recital Hall, 1955 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-159)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Fort Dix Recital Hall, 1955 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-160)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Lost Love, 1968 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-161)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Meisoh (Yoshinaka), 1984 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-162)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Messiah, undated (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-163)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Mozart D minor, 1973 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-164)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano recital 1: Prelude and Fugue in A minor, 1972 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-165)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano recital 2: Sonata opus 2 no. 3, 1972 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-166)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano recital 3: Mazurka A#; Waltz E; Nocturne C#, 1972 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-167)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano recital 4: Sonata in Bb, 1972 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-168)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano concert reel 1: Chopin, Schubert, 1973 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-169)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano concert reel 2: Schubert, 1973 (Box AV21, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-170)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano concert reel 3: Mozart, Chopin, 1973 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-171)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Piano concert reel 4: Encore; Mozart; speeches, 1974 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-172)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Program: Bach/Busconi; Schubert; Chopin, 1974 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-173)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Prokofiev sonata, 1954 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-174)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital 1hr., 1964 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-175)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital reel 1, 1964 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-176)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital reel 2, 1964 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-177)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital reel 3, 1964 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-178)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital Hall: Chopin; 20th century music, undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-179)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital reel 1: Joplin; Chopin, 1978 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-180)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital reel 2: Joplin; Chopin, 1978 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-181)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital reel 3: Joplin; Chopin, 1978 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-182)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital reel 4: Joplin; Chopin, 1978 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-183)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital Hall, undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-184)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recording session: Church of the Master; spirituals, 1965 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-185)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Reel 1: Scott Joplin; Chopin, 1988 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-186)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Reel 2, 1988 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-187)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Sherlock vignette, 1980 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-188)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Side 1, undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-189)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Side 2`, undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-190)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Side A, 1979 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-191)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Side B, 1979 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-192)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Up the Avenue film score, undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-193)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Virtuoso Noodling and Doodling, 1974 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-194)
    - Roy Eaton performance--We're Much Better Than You (Mary Wallach and Roy Eaton), 1978 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-195)
    - Roy Eaton performance--Recital Hall, undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-196)
    - Archery :40 scratch track, undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-197)
    - Benton & Bowles--Alpha Bits Jackson 5, undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-198)
    - Benton & Bowles--Cuts, undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-199)
    - Benton & Bowles--David, 1968 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-200)
    - Benton & Bowles--Roy Eaton songs, undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-201)
      This Man Said; Lost Love; Buried Bird; Soldier's Lament; Let Me In
    - Benton & Bowles--Hasbro 7 tracks, 1975 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-202)
    - Benton & Bowles--IMH, undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-203)
    - Benton & Bowles--IMH bossa nova music, 1963 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-204)
    - Benton & Bowles--Parliament demo, 1963 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-205)
    - Benton & Bowles--S.C. Johnson Bravo, undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-206)
    - Benton & Bowles--Sixty Seconds to Sell, 1960 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-207)
    - Benton & Bowles--Texaco Special "Dr. Bevacqua", 1972 (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-208)
    - Benton & Bowles--Unguentine demo (Mickey Grant), undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-209)
    - Benton & Bowles--We're Much Better Than You, undated (Box AV22, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-210)
    - Blueberry Sundaes in the Sky (Barberi Paul), 1978 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-211)
    - Burn All Your Bridges, 1978 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-212)
    - Cal Schultz--Girls Laugh solo, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-213)
    - Christmas songs, 1975 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-214)
      The Things I Want This Christmas Day; I Hear Bells
    - Crest tests, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-215)
    - Corinna Manetto--Butterfly; Some Day, 1979 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-216)
    - Don Dannemann songs, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-217)
      Mother and Lover; The Sun Went Down; At the End of It All
    - Disco demo, 1979 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-218)
    - Disco Freak reference mix, 1979 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-219)
    - Distant Dawn (Nick Hollander), undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-220)
    - Drums, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-221)
    - Ethel Pence Fenley, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-222)
    - Every Woman Knows (Carly Simon), undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-223)
    - Farts with music (Ed Caffrey), undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-224)
    - Fireflies (Jeff Jolly), 1971 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-225)
      My Prayer; Fireflies; We'll Make It Now
    - Fred Shannon (Shannon Two Feathers), undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-226)
      Thunderbird; Cindy's Laughing Tree; What Would You Do
    - Fred Shannon (Shannon Two Feathers)--What Would You Do, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-227)
    - Fred Shannon (Shannon Two Feathers)--Home to Me, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-228)
    - Good Samaritan, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-229)
    - Handwriting on the Wall (Danny Staton), 1963 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-230)
    - Infinity Factory--Kids' Math Show for TV; theme for four families, 1977 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-231)
    - Infinity Factory--8 tracks, 1977 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-232)
    - Infinity Factory--I Am the Soul of Africa, 1977 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-233)
    - Infinity Factory--Animation "The Shape of Things", 1977 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-234)
    - Infinity Factory--Renee revised, 1977 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-235)
    - Joy Strings, 1976 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-236)
    - Joyce Gordon, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-237)
    - Let the Music Play (Disco Freak), 1979 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-238)
    - Let the Music Play (I'm a Disco Freak), 1979 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-239)
    - Live a Little, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-240)
    - Live a Little, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-241)
    - Major Bowes, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-242)
    - Make Fear Run Away (Brisker/Heller), 1980 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-243)
    - Mary Hockaday, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-244)
      General Store; Darky; Drums; A Prayer; A Scoundrel to His Spouse; Jesus Understands Me
    - Mender of Broken Hearts (George Williams), 1981 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-245)
    - Mennen scratch track, undated (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-246)
    - Mother demo; Feed the Animals, 1977 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-247)
    - Mother May I, 1968 (Box AV23, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-248)